Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 4"x5"
  - Ann Arbor
    - People
      - Ballard, Reverend (Pilgrim Holiness Church) -- family September 1946, 2 negatives (Box 11)
      - Bauer, Louis C., Jr
        - Baby June 8, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Four generations; baby September 27, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Children November 10, 1955, 4 negatives (Box 11)
        - Children November 28, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Children December 3, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 11)
        - Children December 6, 1957, 4 negatives (Box 11)
      - Bauer child in wheelchair (polio victim?) with others February 12, 1955 (Box 11)
      - Benz, Otto, and wife July 25, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 11)
      - Bergman family December 7, 1952, 2 negatives (Box 11)
      - Bird, Mary Lee -- birthday party March 11, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 11)
      - Bish, Mr. and Mrs. Dale 1952 (Box 12)
      - Bishop, Mr. and Mrs. George -- "oldest married couple," June 17, 1937 (Box 12)
      - Boddy, Leonard -- chemist, King-Seeley -- in workshop May 9, 1935, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Boehm, Dan -- with Automotive Lab car November 30, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Botsford, Don -- family December 6, 1956 (Box 12)
      - Bowler, George -- city meat inspector 1948-1949 (Box 12)
      - Bradfield, Mrs. John February 18, 1942 (Box 12)
      - Brenner woman April 1953 (Box 12)
      - Broadhurst children in cowboy outfits November 26, 1952, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Brokaw, Captain July 28, 1944 (Box 12)
      - Brokaw, R.T. (Box 12)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Airports and Airplanes)
      - Bross, Mrs. Hazel (music teacher) -- girls and women at pianos 1949, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Buchschacher, Gary -- in navy uniform May 17, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Buettner, Josephine circa 1955 (Box 12)
      - Buettner, Bill -- and family August 4, 1957, 4 negatives (Box 12)
      - Buhr, Joseph -- president, Buhr Machine Tool Company circa 1951-1952, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Burgender, Cresence -- in home
        - 1952 (Box 12)
        - January 9, 1955 (Box 12)
      - Burns, Mrs. Miles August 17, 1955 (Box 12)
      - Burrows, Walter -- manager, Western Adjustment and Inspection Company September 28, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Burt, Thomas K. (?) -- Chevrolet Motor Sales 1942 (Box 12)
      - Byrn, Marshall -- assistant professor, University of Michigan -- with airplane October 6, 1950, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Cady, Mr. and Mrs. A.H. -- at home with Christmas cards December 31, 1955 (Box 12)
      - Campbell, Elizabeth -- with dog October 30, 1939 (Box 12)
      - Cannon, Estelle (Mrs. Benjamin B.) -- with daughter? January 27, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Clague, Ashley -- Clague's Grocery and Market 1949 (Box 12)
      - Coffee, Janice -- in Brownie uniform January 4, 1957 (Box 12)
      - Conlins -- with baby December 16, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Conlin, Edward -- with Laird and Schilling in law office circa 1952 (Box 12)
      - Cooley family reunion August 16, 1952 (Box 12)
      - Crawford and Thayer law firm 1953 (Box 12)
      - Crouse, Mrs. -- with camera May 20, 1941 (Box 12)
      - Dale, Malcolm January 1955, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Davis, John -- in boy scout uniform 1948 (Box 12)
      - Dull mother and baby 1952 (Box 12)
      - Feiner, B. (woman) circa 1957 (Box 12)
      - Fingerle children December 10, 1939, 9 negatives (Box 12)
      - Fisher, Lee -- retouching photographs? May 3, 1941 (Box 12)
      - Flynn, John -- sheriff and circuit court officer -- in court January 10, 1937 (Box 12)
      - Fox, Howard -- family June 21, 1959 (Box 12)
      - Francisco family July 1953, 7 negatives (Box 12)
      - Freeman, Dr. -- with family at piano December 9, 1952, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Fuller, Dick, and Doris Hanson
        - December 2, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 12)
        - Dancing and other poses December 1, 1938, 5 negatives (Box 12)
        - Wedding October 12, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Gasser baby August 29, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Gelston, Mrs. Mary -- at home on 100th birthday May 13, 1939, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Gordon, Naomi -- photo printer, Ivory Photo circa 1951 (Box 12)
      - Gorham baby and mother November 24, 1939 (Box 12)
      - Granger, Olive -- children circa 1951 (Box 12)
      - Greenman, Emerson -- University of Michigan professor -- wife and children circa 1949, 4 negatives (Box 12)
      - Gregory family circa 1939 (Box 12)
      - Grieser, Henry (Box 12)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Buildings and Views -- Houses and Businesses -- 303 Wilton)
      - Haab, Grace -- in Girl Scout uniform circa 1957 (Box 12)
      - Haberer, Dr. Bert? -- with hiccups sufferer circa 1940, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Hall, Mrs. -- in home July 18, 1940 (Box 12)
      - Hardy, Patricia Newkirk -- county register of deeds
        - October 17, 1956, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - circa 1956 (Box 12)
      - Hart, Julia and baby October 31, 1939, 5 negatives (Box 12)
      - Hartmann, Don -- airport March 10, 1938 (Box 12)
      - Holtom, Marjorie -- occupational therapist, Michigan State Normal College 1953, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Howard, Harvey -- children September 13, 1956, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Hume family -- with television and other interior views of home 1952, 5 negatives (Box 12)
      - Hutchinson, Neil -- commercial artist (?) at work circa 1937-1938 (Box 12)
      - Hutchinson, Ruth -- wearing bird hat November 1, 1938 (Box 12)
      - Iler, Hollis "Red" -- pharmacist, Calkins-Fletcher -- at work August 10, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Immel, Kenneth -- baby and grandparents (?) July 3, 1953 (Box 12)
      - Immel, Wilson -- Wilson Immel Packing Company 1952 (Box 12)
      - Inglis, James -- family portrait December 20, 1945 (Box 12)
      - Isen baby -- with home interiors circa 1953, 5 negatives (Box 12)
      - James, Mrs. L.K. 1949 (Box 12)
      - Jaycox, Clinton A. 1952, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Jaycox, Mrs. February 1955 (Box 12)
      - Jewell, Bob -- with skeet trophy circa 1954 (Box 12)
      - Jones, Edward and Lavina -- 60th Anniversary July 28, 1956 (Box 12)
      - Kaiser, Dale November 20, 1957 (Box 12)
      - Kays, Nancy 1951 (Box 12)
      - Kazemaier, Mr. and Mrs. 1952 (Box 12)
      - Kearney family 1948, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Kelly, Jim, and wife March 1953 (Box 12)
      - Kenfield family November 23, 1952, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Kenworth, Mary Lou circa 1956, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Kenyon, Reuel -- music teacher 1960s (Box 12)
      - Kielwasser, George. (Box 12)
      - Kipke parents and child December 9, 1932, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Kiebsattel -- mother and children 1948, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Knop family -- 4 generations February 24, 1941 (Box 12)
      - Kohen, Mrs. December 7, 1956 (Box 12)
      - Kolander, Mrs. -- as Mae West 1949 (Box 12)
      - Koolman, Harold 1953 (Box 12)
      - Koyle, Mr. September 2, 1938 (Box 12)
      - LaCoe family circa 1949, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - LaJeunesse, Ralph -- bartender, VFW club March 10, 1954 (Box 12)
      - Laney, Carol circa 1970 (Box 12)
      - Lawhorn, Geneva June 1953, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Lee, A.O. -- woman at desk 1946, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Leerkamp, J.R. -- store manager, Auto Parts Company 1950 (Box 12)
      - Lohman, Paul circa 1949 (Box 12)
      - Long, Marguerite -- at organ October 16, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Lowber, David, children -- Christmas card December 14, 1953, 9 negatives (Box 12)
      - Lum, John, and family (manager, Leo Ping Caf) July 9, 1956 (Box 12)
      - Lyons, Lou 1952 (Box 12)
      - Lyons, Wendell -- general secretary, YMCA 1951 (Box 12)
      - Machowski, Mr. 1951 (Box 12)
      - Mack, Walter and Virginia -- at home May 3, 1942, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Mackie, Vickie -- Girl Scout circa 1957 (Box 12)
      - Magee, Yvonne (child) May 5, 1940 (Box 12)
      - Maier, Professor Norman -- wife and children (twins)
        - December 11, 1940, 4 negatives (Box 12)
        - December 2, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Markham, Cal 1949 (Box 12)
      - Marquardt, Mrs. 1952 (Box 12)
      - Martin, "Whitey," December 2, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Martin children 1948, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Maslin, Bruce(R.T. Maslin and Son -- wholesale tobacco and candy) December 17, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Mason, Doc June 26, 1939 (Box 12)
      - Mason family in home 1950, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Mason woman 1951, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - McDonald, Bud. (Box 12)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Businesses -- Ivory Photo)
      - McDonald, Tom, and family? At home April 21, 1937, 4 negatives (Box 12)
      - McKenzie, Mr. -- in workshop 1948, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Metzger, Walter -- children November 16, 1955, 4 negatives (Box 12)
      - Mielke, Florence circa 1957 (Box 12)
      - Miller, Maxine 1953, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Miller, Mrs. Robert, and baby 1951, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Mitchell, Dan Mitchell -- parents and children December 6, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Morrow family 1951, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Morton, Cora, (black woman; in graduation gown? circa1954 (Box 12)
      - Mueller family November 24, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Murphy, Mrs. Catherine circa 1950 (Box 12)
      - Murray, Henry, and other at reunion December 11, 1954, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Neelands, John and Ralph -- Pretzel Bell proprietors, in office April 29, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Newburn, Mr. -- Educational T.V. Center circa 1959 (Box 12)
      - Newkirk, Patricia
        - 1948, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - 1950 (Box 12)
      - Nielson, Russell -- son November 15, 1956, 6 negatives (Box 12)
      - Niemann family
        - December 5, 1952, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - December 4, 1955 (Box 12)
      - Olsen, Dr. (Lloyd?) and family December 10, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Ore, Jim 1952 (Box 12)
      - Parks, Ray (manager, 8th Street Market) and grocery interior 1951, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Parks, W.H. 1953 (Box 12)
      - Paul, Nancy circa 1956 (Box 12)
      - Payne, Jay H. -- judge, probate court 1950 (Box 12)
      - Peirsol, Reardon and Rhea and children
        - September 25, 1938, 11 negatives (Box 12)
        - Lawn party 1938, 9 negatives (Box 12)
        - Mary Peirsol's Christmas Eve party circa 1940, 5 negatives (Box 12)
      - Pepper children at home 1948, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Phillips, Marian, with wife and baby April 1, 1941 (Box 12)
      - Philp, Mr. and Mrs. -- in home 1951 (Box 12)
      - Pierce, Elsie -- at typewriter April 19, 1937 (Box 12)
      - Pierce, Mel (woman) 1952 (Box 12)
      - Pierce, Mrs. circa 1951 (Box 12)
      - Potter, Josiah (Service manager, King-Seeley)
        (See also: Ann Arbor -- Businesses -- King-Seeley)
        - Son and Daughter December 7, 1953, 3 negatives (Box 12)
        - November 17, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Pray, George Washington -- daguerreotype/ambrotype (Box 12)
      - Price, Hickman, Jr
        - Margaret Price cooking, reading to children and with husband 1949, 6 negatives (Box 12)
        - Margaret Price? October 4, 1950, 4 negatives (Box 12)
      - Price, Mrs. Hickman, Sr.? 1954 (Box 12)
      - Price, Percival?
        - Children 1948, 2 negatives (Box 12)
        - Daughter? 1949, 2 negatives (Box 12)
      - Price -- child playing toy piano February 6, 1942 (Box 12)
      - Pruss, Walter -- children November 14, 1957 (Box 12)
      - Pulte, William (Automobile Club of Michigan)-- at bowling alley December 8, 1936, 3 negatives (Box 12)
      - Raskin, Paul
        - First birthday November 19, 1937, 4 negatives (Box 13)
        - Second birthday November 18, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Read -- boy December 5, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Reed baby April 13, 1953 (Box 13)
      - Reiman and horse April 18, 1938, 9 negatives (Box 13)
      - Rettic, Harold -- in carpentry shop June 17, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Rettick, Harvey -- (Sofflet News Co.) and wife 1948 (Box 13)
      - Rickelmann family November 29, 1954 (Box 13)
      - Riley, Vivian -- friends and home June 21, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Riner, William August 10, 1937 (Box 13)
      - Ripatti, Mrs. Harold January 1954 (Box 13)
      - Rockwood, Horace S. III March 16, 1956 (Box 13)
      - Rokahr, (Martha?-waitress, Old German Restaurant) 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Roos, Sox -- child 1949 (Box 13)
      - Root, Eddie circa 1940 (Box 13)
      - Root, Paul (manager Service Bureau and Medical Credit Exchange) 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Roth -- children 1952 (Box 13)
      - Rowe, R. circa 1937 (Box 13)
      - Sadler, Walter C. -- mayor of Ann Arbor -- in office April 6, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Sallade, Mrs. -- with children December 5, 1953, 4 negatives (Box 13)
      - Saxton, Robert
        - January 1955 (Box 13)
        - August 4, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Sayer, Sam March 31, 1937 (Box 13)
      - Scammon, Richard April 29, 1938 (Box 13)
      - Schaeffer twins. (Box 13)
        (See: Shaffer twins)
      - Schaible -- woman with dog December 20, 1940 (Box 13)
      - Schleffer -- girl -- at home December 7, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Schoenhals, Clyde (salesman)
        - May 1937 (Box 13)
        - Child circa 1937, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Schumaier children -- Saline
        - March 22, 1956 (Box 13)
        - circa 1957, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Scott, Mr. December 1955, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Sekaros
        - Baby circa 1951 (Box 13)
        - Extended family November 26, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Seyfried -- baby circa 1950 (Box 13)
      - Shaffer twins
        - February 19, 1956, 4 negatives (Box 13)
        - January 6, 1958, 4 negatives (Box 13)
      - Sheffer, Bruce (student, University of Michigan) January 30, 1941 (Box 13)
      - Shenk, Mrs. (reading at home) 1950 (Box 13)
      - Shipley baby December 2, 1954 (Box 13)
      - Shoenfield woman August 2, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Shroth, Mrs. Ernestine -- in home circa 1938, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Sidnorra, Frank. (Box 13)
      - Siegler, Lear circa 1960 (Box 13)
      - Simon, Pauline -- young women at Christmas party December 13, 1939 (Box 13)
      - Sinelli, Marguerite. (Box 13)
        (See: Ann Arbor -- Businesses -- Ace Cab Company)
      - Singleton, Dr. Edward, and family 1951, 3 negatives (Box 13)
      - Sligh youth with water skis 1950 (Box 13)
      - Smith, Chuck -- family in home -- Ypsilanti December 15, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Soper baby 1943 (Box 13)
      - Spaulding, Colonel -- in commencement robe June 30, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Spindler, Dave (salesman, Van Boven Shoes?) 1955 (Box 13)
      - Staebler, W. -- with fish circa 1957 (Box 13)
      - Stauch mother and baby April 1, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Steffen, William (electrical welder) -- and tools 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Stegner, John B. (manager -- Local Finance Corporation) circa 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Stein family March 14, 1943 (Box 13)
      - Stofflet, Mr. circa 1950 (Box 13)
      - Stoll brothers 1948, 5 negatives (Box 13)
      - Stone, Mr. and Mrs. February 11, 1957 (Box 13)
      - Stone baby March 8, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Strubby, Mr. 1953 (Box 13)
      - Summer child 1949 (Box 13)
      - Sweet children
        - November 5, 1954, 3 negatives (Box 13)
        - November 4, 1955, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Swisher, John (realtor)
        - With others at Woodland model home September 14, 1956 (Box 13)
        - On television June 20, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Teachant, Seth 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Thayer, Mr. H.C. 1951 (Box 13)
      - Thomas, Mr. and Mrs. John December 10, 1956 (Box 13)
      - Thompson, B. -- children and mother
        - December 12, 1937, 8 negatives (Box 13)
        - November 30, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Thompson, Captain -- baby
        - June 20, 1957 (Box 13)
        - August 13, 1957 (Box 13)
      - Thompson, Polly 1948 (Box 13)
      - Thompson, William John June 18, 1940 (Box 13)
      - Thorpe -- young man 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Tilford, Bob February 20, 1938 (Box 13)
      - Titus, Sara June 20, 1940 (Box 13)
      - Tracey, Dr. -- and family August 28, 1955 (Box 13)
      - Travis, Dr. and Mrs. -- 50th Anniversary 1948, 3 negatives (Box 13)
      - Van Ells, Dave
        - February 27, 1954, 3 negatives (Box 13)
        - Baby November 28, 1956 (Box 13)
      - Van Hope, Mrs. Carl -- son's confirmation circa 1956 (Box 13)
      - Vick, Ernie September 14, 1948 (Box 13)
      - Villany, Francis (clerk at Calkins-Fletcher Drug), and Delores Villany -- in kitchen and in costumes December 7, 1936, 8 negatives (Box 13)
      - Vogt
        - Mother and daughters 1951 (Box 13)
        - Children July 30, 1954, 3 negatives (Box 13)
      - Walker, Paul November 10, 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Walter, Janice circa 1954 (Box 13)
      - Wanty, Murray (Wanty and Reule Men's Wear) July 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Ward children
        - November 14, 1951, 2 negatives (Box 13)
        - November 4, 1952 (Box 13)
        - November 21, 1952 (Box 13)
        - November 20, 1953, 3 negatives (Box 13)
        - November 26, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Watkins, Bernadine circa 1950, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Waxman confirmation May 16, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Weber child (girl) May 5, 1951, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Wedemeyer, George (president, Wedemeyer Electronic Supply Company) 1951, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Weidemaier, Mr. and Mrs. (?) 1952, 4 negatives (Box 13)
      - Weihmiller family November 11, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Weinberg, Nate, and mother? (Mary K. Weinberg?) -- in home with University of Michigan football programs, radio, television, clock 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Whitbeck, Don -- graduation 1951 (Box 13)
      - Welhener children 1949 (Box 13)
      - Wicks mother and baby January 10, 1957 (Box 13)
      - Wild family at home circa 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Willens -- young man 1950 (Box 13)
      - Willner baby 1950 (Box 13)
      - Wilson, J. -- woman (photographic experiment by Ivory -- several views) June 2, 1938, 8 negatives (Box 13)
      - Wilson, Jenny March 15, 1957 (Box 13)
      - Winchell, Robert (Allen Quimby Veneer Co.) -- family at home November 18, 1954, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Wirth, Jack circa 1953, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Windell children 1949, 3 negatives (Box 13)
      - Wisely (Mr. and Mrs.?) Ira F. -- in front 1209 Clague house decorated for Christmas December 20, 1960 (Box 13)
      - Wixson, Dick (student) April 9, 1941 (Box 13)
      - Wolff, Mr. and Mrs. Ted (building contractor) circa 1945 (Box 13)
      - Woods, L.A. -- children 1954 (Box 13)
      - Wright, Lisa (child of Don Wright) -- in home circa 1949 (Box 13)
      - Wurster, Robert -- children 1948 (Box 13)
      - Yek woman 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Young, Mrs. -- in garden circa 1952, 3 negatives (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Young girl 1930s, 3 negatives (Box 13)
        - Newsboy at Nickels Arcade May 13, 1932, 2 negatives (Box 13)
        - Young women in boiler room (?) August 21, 1939 (Box 13)
        - Men in motor boat -- Calvert's Reserve 1947 (Box 13)
        - Sunoco employee ("Al") August 3, 1955 (Box 13)
    - Pets and Other Animals
      - Alligator and man September 7, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 13)
      - Cat 1948, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Cows circa 1948 (Box 13)
      - Dogs 1936-1957, 8 negatives (Box 13)
      - Hogs December 28, 1953, 7 negatives (Box 13)
      - Squirrel -- woman feeding squirrel at Van's Market January 6, 1954 (Box 13)
    - Politics
      - Murray Van Wagoner gubernatorial campaign September 2, 1940 (Box 13)
      - Window display on voting 1952, 2 negatives (Box 13)
      - Peter Darrow and Democrats, including Governor and Mrs. G. Mennen Williams and Neil Staebler circa 1956, 8 negatives (Box 13)
      - Vandalism at Congressmen George Meader's campaign headquarters, early 1960s, 3 negatives (Box 13)
    - Social Life and Customs
      - Community Events
        - Marching band on North University 1910 (Box 13)
        - Circus people February 9, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 13)
        - Soap box derby July 26, 1941, 8 negatives (Box 13)
        - 1950
          - Community sing (Box 13)
          - Play (Box 13)
          - Larry McQueen day, 7 negatives (Box 13)
        - Christmas sing 1953 (Box 13)
        - Dramatic Arts Theater circa 1954 (Box 13)
        - Organist circa 1956, 2 negatives (Box 13)
        - Musicians' Local 625 -- Winter Jamboree February 16, 1968, 24 negatives (in 11 envelope) (Box 13)
      - Dance Bands and Orchestras 1954-1965, 20 negatives (Box 13)
      - Funerals 1937-1954, 23 negatives (Box 13)
      - Parties 1937-1953, 19 negatives (Box 14)
      - Radio and Television Broadcasts 1947-1955, 15 negatives (Box 14)
      - Sports
        - Baseball 1940-1956, 19 negatives (Box 14)
        - Golf June 10, 1940, 4 negatives (Box 14)
        - Horseback riding March 17, 1940 (Box 14)
        - Hunting trip 1952, 30 negatives (in 20 envelope) (Box 14)
        - Ice Skating 1948-1954, 15 negatives (Box 14)
        - Roller Skating 1943-1945, 3 negatives (Box 14)
      - Weddings 1938-1960s, 190 negatives (Box 14)
    - World War II
      - Army recruiting circa 1930s (Box 14)
      - WPA Project -- air raid defense October 12, 1939 (Box 14)
      - October 22, 1940
        - Ann Arbor draft board, 2 negatives (Box 14)
        - Company K leaving by train, 9 negatives (Box 14)
      - Draftees at depot January 21, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 14)
      - Aluminum drive July 1941, 2 negatives (Box 14)
      - Sailor and woman November 22, 1941 (Box 14)
      - Draft? April 27, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 14)
      - Guards at Armory April 27, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 14)
      - Bomber plant flight division -- group photo May 14, 1942 (Box 14)
      - Dr. Maddock's base hospital -- leaving from depot June 27, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 14)
      - Women selling savings bonds on campus August 17, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 14)
      - Armistice Day parade November 10, 1942 (Box 14)
      - Boy Scouts' aluminum drive, ca 1942, 2 negatives (Box 14)
      - Exhibit of war heroes 1946, 2 negatives (Box 14)
  - University of Michigan
    - Alumni Activities
      - Alumnae Club: "Information Please" Fundraiser January 20, 1940, 4 negatives (Box 15)
      - Alumnae Council: Mrs. Lucile Conger
        - Group October 26, 1937 (Box 15)
        - House Site with group of women November 10, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 15)
        - Luncheon November 5, 1941 (Box 15)
        - Memorabilia
          - Centennial Plates and Saucers August 10, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 15)
          - Tablecloth May 20, 1940 (Box 15)
          - Miscellaneous 1941, 4 negatives (Box 15)
        - Tea November 7, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 15)
      - Alumni
        - circa 1937, 11 negatives (Box 15)
        - June 15, 1940, 20 negatives (Box 15)
        - Undated
          - E. Lovejoy (Law) and unidentified man (Box 15)
          - On steps of Rackham, late circa 1930s (Box 15)
          - Fixel 1950 copy negatives, 2 negatives (Box 15)
      - Alumni Association
        - Morgan (Bob) and Projector 1943 (Box 15)
        - Tapping(T. Hawley) group circa 1950 (Box 15)
          (See also: UM -- Individuals -- Staff -- Tapping)
          (See also: UM -- Individuals -- Staff -- Wilfred B. Shaw)
      - Fraternities
        - Acacia 50th Anniversary (includes exterior of 1923 Geddes) August 1954, 32 negatives (Box 15)